Zachary Upstone

Email: Zac.upstone@gmail.com LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/zachary-upstone-076218214/
Telephone: 07591 701760 Website: https://zu213.github.io/#/zach-upstone

Personal Profile	
	I am a recent graduate with a Degree in Computer Science from the University of Bath.
	I have extensive experience in customer-facing jobs, including McDonalds
	and Bar work, showing I am an adaptable and enthusiastic worker who is
	confident dealing with the public.
	I am also a good team worker, reliable and trustworthy having experience
F1 (1	working on group projects throughout university and my placement.
Education	
2020 - 2024	University of Bath – Computer Science BSc – First Class Honours.
	Units including: Advanced graphics processing, Logic and semantics of programming languages, Entrepreneurship and Reinforcement learning.
2013 - 2020	Chesham Grammar School
2010 2020	A level: Further Mathematics (A), Mathematics (A*), Computer Science (A),
	Physics (A).
	GCSE's: 4 grades 9's, 2 grade 8's, 3 grades 6's, 1 grade 5, 1 grade A.
Work Experience	
July 2022 - June 2023	• Student software developer at Bsquare, during which I had to
Na. 2004 I 2000	respond to many tasks and issues, be flexible and ready to learn.
Nov 2021 - June 2022	 Bar staff at the Students Union at the University of Bath, I dealt with customers' requests serving drinks, cleaning and operating a till.
July 2021 - Oct 2021	 Crew member at McDonalds, I worked at multiple station in
Odly 2021 Odl 2021	McDonalds showing flexibility and ability to work in a team.
July 2020 - Sept 2020	Assistant Gardener at RM Gardening, this included manual labour
,	and dealing with customers' requests, developing my tenacity and
	adaptability to different workplace environments.
Technical skills	
	Till and cash handling experience from McDonalds and the SU bar
	Customer service skills from SU bar
	Inventory management from McDonalds Food sefety and byging training from McDonalds
	 Food safety and hygiene training from McDonalds Full UK driver's license
	Computer literacy from degree and placement
Achievements	comparer meraej nem degree und pracement
	Gold DofE
	 Competed in BathHack 2021 and 2024 using React
	 Employee of the month August 2021 at McDonalds
<u>Interests</u>	
	I have a keen interest in art and design, producing collages, clay sculptures
	and prints using spray techniques. I also enjoy exercise, going to the gym
Deferences	and swimming regularly.
References	Lochlann Ryan Alan Hayes
	Assistant Manager at the Student Personal tutor at the University
	Union at the University of Bath of Bath
	LR616@bath.ac.uk AH347@bath.ac.uk
	_